[Team leader Baek Su Jeong]
[قائد الفريق بايك سو جونغ]
[Moon Ga Young]
[نحن مازلنا شباب]
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[المخرج بان جو يون]
[Choi Hyeon Wook]
[تشوي هيون ووك]
[The heir of Yongsung. Is there a new Chaebol director?]
[خليفة يونغ سونغ. مدير جديد لشركة تشايبول؟]
[Im Se Mi]
[إم سي مي]
[Kwak Shi Yang]
[كواك سي يانغ]
My Dearest Nemesis
[عدوتي العزيزة]
[This drama is entirely fictional.]
[هذه الدراما خيالية.]
~ Episode 7 ~
[الحلقة 7]
You'll recognize them.
لقد تعرفت عليه.
This is the brand I use.
إنها العلامة التجارية التي أستخدمها.
I only use their products.
أستخدم منتجاتهم فقط.
Just like the singer of my favorite band.
وهذا ما يفعله أيضًا مطرب فرقتي المفضلة.
Su Jeong?
سو جونغ؟
What's up?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm sorry, Ji Wu, but...
أنا آسف، جي وو، ولكن...
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[المخرج بان جو يون]
I'm sorry. Just a second.
انا اسف.ثانية واحدة فقط.
Yes.
نعم.
Forgiveness?
عفو؟
I'm currently in a department store. Why—
أنا في المتجر الآن. لماذا-
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Was?
ماذا؟
Something wrong?
هل هناك شيء خاطئ؟
No, everything is fine.
لا، إنه لا شيء.
Shall we go then?
هل نذهب إذن؟
Secure.
بالتأكيد.
What's it like here?
كيف هذا؟
It's simple. I think it suits you.
إنه أمر بسيط، أعتقد أنه يناسبك.
That's good. I like it.
هذا جميل، أنا أحبه.
The size is...
الحجم هو...
One moment.
لحظة واحدة فقط
Secure.
بالتأكيد.
Forgiveness.
اعذرني.
Director.
مخرج.
You can't walk around here like that.
لا يمكنك أن تكون هنا وتبدو بهذا الشكل.
You tried so hard to hide it.
لقد حاولت جاهدا إخفاء ذلك.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I know it's crazy, but—
أعرف أن هذا جنون أيضًا، لكن-
- But why are you here? — I remember everything.
- ولكن لماذا أنت هنا؟ - أتذكر كل شيء.
That was...
كان ذلك...
My first kiss.
قبلتي الاولى.
Man, why isn't it opening?
يا إلهي، لماذا لا يفتح؟
Man.
يا إلهي.
How strange.
كم هو غريب
What do we do now?
ماذا نفعل؟
What's up?
ما هو الخطأ؟
The door won't open.
الباب لن يفتح.
Nobody went in there.
لم يدخل أحد.
Stay here.
ابقى هنا.
Oh my goodness!
يا إلهي!
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
يا إلهي، أنا آسف.
I didn't know you were in there.
لم أكن أعلم أنك كنت هناك.
Su Jeong, why were you in there...?
سو جونغ، لماذا كنت هناك...
I checked to see if I had my top on backwards.
كنت أتأكد من أنني أرتدي قميصي مقلوبًا.
I probably scared you because I didn't reply.
لابد أنني فاجأتك لأنني لم أجيب.
What about your size? Have you found one?
ماذا عن مقاسك هل وجدت أي مقاس؟
- Well, no. - That's right.
- حسنًا، لا. - صحيح.
My size, in particular, is no longer available.
كان ينقصني فقط مقاسي.
Then we can look for something else.
بإمكاننا أن نحاول شيئًا آخر إذن.
That. That there. I love that.
هذا. هذا. أنا أحب هذا.
The gray. The gray. The gray.
هذا الرمادي. ذاك الرمادي. ذاك الرمادي.
What's the grey one like? It's so pretty.
كيف حال اللون الرمادي؟ إنه جميل جدًا.
Do you know his size?
هل لديك حجمه؟
Could you check?
هل ستكون قادرا على التحقق؟
- Well, sure. Just a moment. - O-okay.
- حسنًا، نعم. لحظة واحدة فقط. - حسنًا.
White clothes get dirty so quickly.
الملابس البيضاء تتلف بسهولة.
This one has a beautiful pattern.
هذا لديه نمط لطيف.
Are you continuing your search here?
هل يمكنك التحقق من هذا الجانب؟
I'll look over there.
سأذهب للتحقق من ذلك هناك.
That's pretty. That too.
هذا جميل، وهذا أيضًا جميل.
Thank you for going shopping with me, Su Jeong.
شكرا لك على التسوق معي، سو جونغ.
When are you free next?
متى ستكون حرًا في المرة القادمة؟
Oh well...
حسنًا...
I don't think I'll be able to meet you again.
لا أعتقد أنني سأتمكن من رؤيتك في المرة القادمة.
Team leader Baek Su Jeong.
قائد الفريق بايك سو جونغ.
There is urgent work to be done. What are you doing here?
هناك عمل عاجل يجب القيام به. ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Please?
عفو؟
There's no time to lose. Follow me.
ليس هناك وقت نضيعه، اتبعني.
Wait, Director...
انتظر يا مدير...
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Is OK.
لا بأس.
You can leave.
يمكنك الذهاب.
Sorry.
أنا آسف.
I am so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
Also,
لذا،
All you want is fun.
استمتع بها كما تريد
You can't behave like that.
لا يمكنك التصرف بهذه الطريقة.
I was cornered.
لقد وضعت في موقف صعب.
I already feel bad because of him.
لقد شعرت بالأسف تجاهه بالفعل.
I don't feel sorry for this man.
لا أشعر بالأسف تجاه هذا الرجل.
- What? - By the way,
- ماذا؟ - بالمناسبة،
I'm sorry I don't remember the kiss.
أنا آسف لأنني لم أتذكر القبلة.
I apologize for that.
أعتذر عن ذلك.
Are you apologizing now?
هل تعتذر الآن؟
Well, okay. I'll accept them.
حسنًا، سأقبل ذلك.
I'm just going to pretend it never happened anyway.
قررت أن أعتقد أن هذا لم يحدث أبدًا، على أي حال.
Never happened?
لم يحدث أبدا؟
Wouldn't it be easier for us if we both continued to develop ourselves?
ألا سيكون الأمر أسهل لكلا منا في المستقبل؟
I think you're misunderstanding.
أعتقد أنك مخطئ.
I apologize for not remembering.
لقد اعتذرت فقط عن عدم التذكر.
I'm not sorry I kissed you. That was...
أنا لست آسفة لأنني قبلتك، لقد كان ذلك...
No error.
ليس خطأ.
Oh well.
حسنًا...
if it wasn't a mistake...
لو لم يكن خطأ...
It wasn't a mistake.
لم يكن خطأ.
It's not like I did it for no reason.
It's not like I did it for no reason.
[Unnie Jin]
[Jin unni]
Um...
Um...
I just remembered that I have a date with someone.
I just remembered I'm meeting someone.
I-I'll talk to you later.
I-I'll talk to you later.
Worth...
Wait...
Is she shy?
Is she shy?
Now I understand.
I can see that.
She is more shy than I thought.
She's shyer than I thought.
Are you so aroused by the date?
Are you all burning up from the date?
Unnie!
Unni!
I asked if your heart perceived the feelings.
I was asking if your heart was feeling the passion.
What are you thinking about?
What are you thinking?
So? Will you continue to see him?
So? Will you keep seeing him?
No. I turned him down.
No. I turned him down.
What why?
What? Why?
I thought it was working well.
I thought he seemed all right.
You didn't like him this time?
You didn't like him this time?
He worked well again this time.
He seemed all right this time, too.
That's what I said.
That's what I'm saying.
He's your ideal guy.
He's the type you wanted.
He is older, has a secure job
He's older, has a stable job,
and has a down-to-earth taste and personality.
and has a down-to-earth taste and personality.
That's true.
Yeah.
I don't like younger men and I hate those with strange taste.
I don't like younger men,
So, what's the problem?
So, what's the issue?
Do you have...
Do you...
Perhaps someone else is on your mind?
have someone else in mind, by chance?
One highball, please.
A highball, please.
Okay.
Okay.
Come immediately.
Coming.
No.
No.
I like this guy?
I like that guy?
Absolutely not.
There's no way.
I wore that.
I was wearing this.
Did that make me more attractive to her?
Is that why she found me more attractive?
How could I forget such a precious memory?
How could I forget such a precious memory?
Not...
Don't...
Never come near Makgeolli, Ban Ju Yeon.
Don't ever go anywhere near makgeolli, Ban Ju Yeon.
[Music for sleeping]
[Music for sleeping]
It was not a mistake.
It wasn't a mistake.
It's not like I did it for no reason.
It's not like I did it for no reason.
So what now?
What now, then?
Does he want to go out or something?
Does he want to go out or something?
He is the same age as Su Bin. Same age.
He's the same age as Su Bin. The same age.
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[Director Ban Ju Yeon]
[He kisses for 6,000 won]
[He Kisses for 6,000 Won]
I'm not like that guy.
I'm not like this guy.
What is he talking about?
What's he talking about?
He's so funny.
He's so funny.
Please believe me.
Please believe me.
What is he saying?
What's he saying?
What is that?
What's this?
Damn, I don't know?
Gosh, I don't know!
You said, "We'll talk later."
You said, "Talk to you later."
When exactly is "later"?
When is "later," exactly?
[Team leader Beak Su Jeong]
[Team Leader Baek Su Jeong]
That's too formal.
It's too formal.
Nevertheless... [Ban Ju Yeon / Baek Su Jeong]
Still... [Ban Ju Yeon / Baek Su Jeong]
We kissed once.
we kissed once.
[Contact]
[Friend info]
[Contact: Baek Su Jeong]
[Friend info: Ms. Baek Su Jeong]
Sometimes you have to wait.
Sometimes you have to wait.
I will see her tomorrow.
I'll see her tomorrow.
Let's not be too hasty.
Let's not be hasty.
Su Jeong.
Su Jeong.
I heard your girlfriend rejected the man.
I heard your friend rejected that man.
Yes. How do you know that?
Yes. How did you know?
Hey, his mother is apparently crying because of that.
Hey, his mom is apparently crying about it
and says the woman must be snobbish.
saying the woman must be snobby.
Seriously! I told you to go on a date instead.
Geez! I told you to go on a date instead.
Not many men can tolerate a woman with flaws.
Not many men are okay with a flawed woman.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Am I the woman with flaws?
Am I the flawed woman?
That's right. Why did you have to get divorced?
That's right. Why did you have to get divorced?
Why is getting a divorce a mistake?
Why is getting divorced a flaw?
I mean, you couldn't control your temper.
I mean, you couldn't control your temper
And that's why you destroyed a perfect family.
and destroyed a perfectly good family.
Do you think someone can do something like that in their right mind?
You can't do that in the right mind.
Now you know how bad it was for me.
That's how bad it was for me.
Anyway, it's fine if I hear that, but don't say it to anyone else.
Anyway, I'm fine hearing that
If you say that getting a divorce is a mistake, someone will hate you for it.
If you say getting divorced is a flaw,
I'm not the only one who says that.
I'm not the only one who says that.
Everyone thinks you're flawed.
Everyone thinks you're flawed.
Many people don't think that. Really...
- A lot of people don't. - Aigoo...
It's just you. Just you.
It's just you. Just you.
I'm serious. There's someone else.
I'm serious. There's someone else.
Is it a man?
Is it a man?
Seriously.
Seriously.
You can't stop thinking about men, can you?
You can't stop thinking about men, can you?
Let me meet him if he's a man.
Let me meet him if it's a man.
Why? Do you want to date him?
Why? Will you date him?
My goodness, my goodness, you little one!
أيغو، أيغو، أيها الصغير.
You're a little snot-nosed brat, aren't you?
أنت طفل صغير، أليس كذلك؟
Dad, Mom wants to date other men.
أبي وأمي يريدون مواعدة رجال آخرين.
Hey, Seo Ha Jin,
مرحبا، سيو ها جين،
Stop annoying your mother.
لا تضايق أمك.
She's only doing this because she's worried about you.
لأنها قلقة عليك
Man, I'm so unlucky because I'm single.
آه، يا مسكين أنا لأنني أعزب.
Are you looking for someone?
هل تبحث عن شخص ما؟
I assure you, I do not.
أؤكد لك أنني لست كذلك.
Let's go upstairs. We have a lot of important things to do.
دعنا نصعد، لدينا الكثير من الأمور المهمة التي يجب القيام بها.
Seok Hui,
سوك هوي
Why are you doing this yourself?
لماذا تفعل هذا بنفسك؟
Because it's my job.
لأنها وظيفتي.
I know, but give them to me.
أنا أعلم ذلك، ولكن أعطني إياهم.
- I'll wear them. - That's fine.
- سأحملهم. - أنا بخير.
No.
لا.
Nun...
حسنًا...
- Hello Hello.
- مرحبا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Team leader, aren't you joining?
قائد الفريق، هل أنت متورط؟
- Team Leader Baek─ - Deputy Jeong.
- قائد الفريق بايك- - نائب جونغ.
Yes.
نعم.
Are Ludwig, Friedrich, Heinrich, Carlos and Barbarossa doing well?
هل لودفيج، فريد، هاينريش، كارلوس، وبارباروسا بخير؟
How do you know the names of my dogs?
كيف تعرف أسماء كلابي؟
Even my parents don't know.
حتى والدي لا يعلمون.
Of course I know them.
بالطبع أفعل.
I heard you saved her.
سمعت أنك أنقذتهم.
I have always admired your kindness.
لقد أعجبت بلطفك دائمًا.
I am so touched.
أنا متأثرة جداً.
What the hell?
ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
Na Na, that's it.
نا نا، تناول هذا.
- I'll eat somewhere else. - What?
- سأتناول الطعام بالخارج. - ماذا؟
Why is she avoiding me?
لماذا تستمر في تجنبي؟
[I am the devil]
[أنا الشيطان]
[Pros / Cons]
[الايجابيات / السلبيات]
[Pros: None / Cons: Too young, bad style...]
[الايجابيات: لا يوجد / السلبيات: صغير جدًا، أسلوب سيء...]
[Pros: Nothing / Cons: Dragon tattoo...]
[الايجابيات: لا يوجد / السلبيات: وشم التنين...]
Are these the only things they are?
هل كل هذا مثل هذا؟
[Cannot tolerate anything (bad memory), music hurts the ears...]
[خفيفة الوزن (ذاكرة رهيبة)، الموسيقى تؤذي الأذنين...]
[Number 1 DIY store]
[رقم 1 في الأجهزة]
Oh my goodness, I'm dying.
يا إلهي، أنا أموت.
The Yongsung department store has Director Ban,
متجر يونغسونغ يرشح المدير بان
the grandson of the chairwoman Jeong Hyo Seon,
حفيد رئيسة مجلس الإدارة جونغ هيو سيون
proposed to work on a huge renovation project.
للعمل على مشروع تجديد كبير
Director Ban has avoided the public eye;
لقد كان المخرج بان يتجنب التعرض
However, he has now officially announced his existence.
ومع ذلك، فقد أعلن عن وجوده رسميًا.
Many see this as a precursor to his appointment.
يتوقع الكثيرون أن تكون هذه خطوة تمهيدية لتجهيزه
as successor.
كخليفة
- The clearer the succession becomes... - Wow, he is...
- عندما تصبح الخلافة واضحة... - واو، لقد كان...
A truly impressive man.
رجل مثير للإعجاب.
Team leader, the promotional post is online.
قائد الفريق، المقال الترويجي جاهز.
I will send you the link.
سأرسل لك الرابط.
Okay. I'll take a look at it right away.
حسنًا، سأتحقق من ذلك على الفور.
I guess the PR team also added the story of Director Ban.
أعتقد أن فريق العلاقات العامة أضاف قصة المخرج بان أيضًا.
And the public reaction is currently explosive.
والرد العام الآن متفجر.
It looks like he will officially become the successor.
يبدو أنه الخليفة رسميًا.
That's great.
هذا رائع.
We live in different worlds. Seriously.
نحن نعيش في عالمين مختلفين، بجدية.
[Yongsung = Golden Spoon]
[يونجسونج = ملعقة فضية]
[I envy the employees of Yongsung]
[أنا غيور من موظفي يونغسونغ]
I know.
أنا أعرف.
How could I have forgotten that?
كيف نسيت هذا الأمر؟
I have no reason to think about it.
لم يكن لدي سبب للتفكير.
[Trash can]
[نفاية]
I have no reason to avoid it. So why am I doing it?
ليس لدي سبب لتجنبه. لماذا أفعل هذا؟
That's correct.
أنا أعرف.
It's not like you can just keep doing that.
ليس من الممكن أن تستمر في فعل هذا.
We didn't want to talk to each other. Why do you continue to avoid me?
كان من المفترض أن نتحدث، لماذا تستمر في تجنبي؟
You are nice to everyone.
أنت ودود مع الجميع.
What did you want to talk about?
ماذا تريد أن تتحدث عنه؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
I don't think our kiss was a mistake.
لا أعتقد أن قبلتنا كانت خطأ.
I'm not going to pretend it never happened, so...
لن أتظاهر بأن هذا لم يحدث أبدًا، لذا...
- unless you don't like me and avoid me─ - Director,
- إلا إذا كنت تكرهني وتتجنبني- - المخرج،
I think you forgot. We're at work.
أعتقد أنك نسيت، نحن في العمل.
You are the director.
أنت المخرج.
Not just any director, but Yongsung's heir.
ليس أي مخرج بل خليفة يونغسونغ.
And I am your subordinate.
وأنا مرؤوسك.
You don't want to let it rest?
ألا تريد أن تترك الأمر يمر دون أن تدري؟
What do you want to do then?
ماذا ستفعل إذن؟
Will you hold my hand?
هل ستمسك يدي؟
Can you hold my hand and go outside?
هل يمكنك أن تمسك يدي وتذهب للخارج؟
Can you imagine yourself like this...
هل تستطيع الوقوف...؟
Stand in front of people and the chairperson?
أمام الناس ورئيسة المجلس؟
I don't want that either.
أنا أيضا لا أريد ذلك.
I am not interested in being fired.
أنا لا أرغب في أن يتم طردي.
Also...
لذا...
We have nothing to discuss.
ليس لدينا ما نتحدث عنه.
We don't have to.
نحن لا نحتاج إلى ذلك.
I...
أنا...
♫ ♫
♫ في نهاية اللحظات الخافتة ♫
I think you understand what I mean.
دعنا نقول فقط أنك فهمت ما قلته.
Have you forgotten that I confessed my feelings to you?
هل نسيت أنني اعترفت لك بمشاعري؟
Oh, that?
أوه، هذا؟
Have you forgotten that I said "no"??
هل نسيت أنني قلت لا؟
If that's why you came here, I find that somewhat unpleasant.
إذا كان هذا هو السبب الذي جعلك تأتي إلى هنا
I thought you had gone home.
اعتقدت أنك ذهبت إلى المنزل.
I was just lost in thought.
أنا خارج عن نطاق السيطرة قليلاً الآن.
Come in. Come in.
ادخل. ادخل.
Yes.
نعم.
What? She's getting married?
ماذا؟ سي وون سيتزوج؟
Our classmate?
زميلنا في الصف؟
Yes, it seems like only yesterday that she was chasing after you in 12th grade.
نعم، يبدو الأمر وكأنه كان بالأمس
She probably wasn't the only one.
أفترض أنها لم تكن الوحيدة
She wants to hand us the invitation in person.
إنها تريد أن تقدم لنا الدعوة شخصيًا
Okay.
تمام.
Have you finished work yet?
صواب، هل تركت العمل؟
Should we go for a drink if you have time?
هل يجب علينا أن نتناول مشروبًا إذا كنت متاحًا؟
Agreed. Sounds good.
صفقة تبدو جيدة
Shall we meet again at Sulo?
هل يجب أن نلتقي في سولو مرة أخرى؟
Let's go somewhere else.
دعنا نذهب إلى مكان آخر.
I'm not going there anymore.
سأتوقف عن الذهاب إلى هناك.
Why? The food was good.
لماذا؟ كان طعامهم جيدًا.
Because I don't want her to feel uncomfortable in my presence.
لأنني لا أستطيع أن أجعلها تشعر بالانزعاج.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Was?
هاه؟ أعتقد أنني ذهبت إلى هناك مرات عديدة.
I will never go there again.
لن أعود إلى هناك مرة أخرى أبدًا.
[Grace]
[جمال]
What am I doing here?
ماذا أفعل هنا؟
I thought I was on my way home.
اعتقدت أنني في طريقي إلى المنزل.
♫ Everything has already been said and done ♫
♫ لقد قيل وفعل كل شيء ♫
You're welcome.
هنا تذهب.
♫ And everything you hear, ♫
♫ وكل ما تسمعه ♫
♫ I know there's nothing I can say that you haven't already heard ♫
♫ أعلم أنه لا يوجد شيء أستطيع قوله ولم تسمعه ♫
♫ Although I can tell you for sure ♫
♫ على الرغم من أنني متأكد من أنني سأخبرك ♫
♫ Darling, don't worry ♫
♫ عزيزتي، لا تقلقي ♫
♫ Don't be afraid of the darkness ♫
♫ لا تخجل من الظلام ♫
♫ The blankets will keep you warm ♫
♫ دع الأغطية تبقيك دافئًا ♫
♫ We can weather the storm ♫
♫ يمكننا أن نواجه العاصفة ♫
It is said that distance makes affection grow.
يقال أن الغياب يجعل القلب أكثر شوقاً.
You were mentioned several times at the last supervisory board meeting.
لقد تم ذكرك في اجتماع مجلس الإدارة الأخير
and everyone reacted positively.
وتفاعل الجميع بشكل إيجابي.
They also seemed enthusiastic about the renovation project.
لقد بدوا متحمسين لمشروع التجديد أيضًا.
Good to hear.
من الجيد سماع ذلك.
Since they were officially introduced,
منذ أن تم تقديمك رسميًا،
People seem to be treating you differently now.
يبدو أن الناس يعاملونك بطريقة مختلفة جدًا.
Because I have a greater responsibility,
لأن لدي مسؤولية أكبر،
I should work harder.
ينبغي لي أن أعمل بجدية أكبر.
You are the director.
أنت المخرج
Not just any director, but Yongsung's legacy.
ليس أي مخرج، بل خليفة يونغ سونغ.
And I am your employee.
وأنا مرؤوسك
Also...
لذا...
There's nothing to discuss.
ليس لدينا ما نتحدث عنه
We don't need that.
نحن لا نحتاج إلى ذلك
She even looked beautiful at that moment.
لقد بدت جميلة حتى في تلك اللحظة.
Baek Su Jeong.
بايك سو جونغ.
I saw the article.
لقد رأيت المقال.
That was a good photo. When did you take it?
كانت تلك صورة جميلة متى التقطتها؟
Do you have anything carbonated? Or coffee?
هل لديك أي شيء غازي أو قهوة؟
I don't have any. Drink this.
انا لا اشرب هذا.
Correct.
نعم.
I should drink cold water and wake up.
ينبغي لي أن أشرب الماء البارد وأستيقظ.
What's suddenly going on?
ماذا يحدث فجأة؟
I just wanted to congratulate you.
أردت فقط أن أهنئك.
By the way, do I need a reason to visit you?
بالمناسبة، هل أحتاج إلى سبب لزيارتك؟
Don't you think so?
ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
To be honest,
صراحة،
I had the feeling that I needed to go somewhere.
شعرت أنني يجب أن أذهب إلى مكان ما.
Otherwise, I would have gone back there.
أو كنت سأعود إلى هناك مرة أخرى.
Ju Yeon,
جو يون،
Do you know why General Kim Yu Sin
هل تعلم لماذا الجنرال كيم يو سين
has beheaded his horse?
قطع رأس حصانه؟
Do you mean General Kim Yu Sin, who was born in the year 595?
هل تقصد الجنرال كيم يو سين؟
He is an admirable general,
إنه مثير للإعجاب كجنرال، ولكن
But he blamed his horse for his weak willpower.
ألقى باللوم على إرادته الضعيفة على حيوان بريء.
- Why? - Hm?
- لماذا؟ - هاه؟
Yes.
نعم.
Yes you are right.
نعم، أنت على حق.
But I can understand how he felt.
ولكنني أستطيع أن أفهم كيف شعر.
I can't tie myself up.
ليس الأمر وكأنني قادر على ربط نفسي.
My head tells me I shouldn't...
رأسي يقول أنني لا ينبغي
But I miss her.
لكنني أفتقدها باستمرار.
Is that the reason?
هل هذا هو السبب؟
My body always goes to her.
جسدي يستمر بالذهاب إليها.
Goodness, I need to pull myself together.
يا إلهي، أنا بحاجة إلى أن أجمعها معًا.
One always acts with the heart,
قلب المرء دائما
before you do it with your head.
أفعال أمام الرأس.
Is this what it means to like someone...?
هل هذا ما يعنيه أن تحب شخصًا بصدق؟
That I really can't give up?
بصراحة لا أستطيع الاستسلام؟
[Yongsung Kaufhaus]
[متجر يونغسونغ]
Good morning
صباح الخير.
Ah yes.
حسنا، نعم.
Yes, we agreed to meet again tomorrow for lunch.
نعم، سوف نلتقي مرة أخرى لتناول الغداء غدًا.
I will send out invitations.
إنها متعة بالنسبة لي.
Do you know Baekyonggak?
هل تعرف بايكيونجاك؟
I've heard it's difficult to make a reservation there.
سمعت أن هناك حجزًا هناك.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I admire the effort.
أعجبني هذا المجهود.
But I will pay for the food.
ولكنني سأدفع ثمن الوجبة.
Oh...
نعم...
In order.
حسنًا.
Who are you meeting up with?
من ستلتقي؟
Is this the man I saw you with in the department store?
هل يمكن أن يكون هذا الرجل الذي رأيته في المتجر؟
That's personal.
إنه أمر شخصي.
I don't think I need to answer that, Director.
لا أعتقد أنني بحاجة للإجابة، يا مدير.
Yes, we agreed to meet again tomorrow for lunch.
سوف نلتقي مرة أخرى لتناول الغداء غدًا.
Do you know Baekyonggak?
هل تعرف بايك يونج جااك؟
I've heard it's difficult to make a reservation there.
سمعت أن هناك حجزًا هناك.
I thought I should do that.
اعتقدت أنني يجب أن أفعل ذلك.
- Is he crazy? - It could be a surprise.
- هل هو مجنون؟ - قد تكون مفاجأة.
Man, what should I do?
يا إلهي، ماذا أفعل؟
Who is this man?
من هو هذا الرجل الآن؟
Stop!
قف!
That's enough now.
هذا يكفي.
Director.
مخرج.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Father?
أب؟
Su Bin's girlfriend?
صديقة سو بين؟
Didn't you say you'd met her before?
ألم تقل أنك التقيت بها مرة واحدة؟
Yes, we've agreed to meet for lunch tomorrow.
نعم، سوف نلتقي مرة أخرى لتناول الغداء غدًا.
It is a pleasure for me.
إنها متعة بالنسبة لي.
Lunch? Where?
الغداء؟ أين؟
Do you know Baekyonggak?
هل تعرف بايكيونجاك؟
I heard there's a reservation there.
سمعت أن هناك حجزًا هناك.
This is a famous restaurant.
هذا مطعم مشهور.
But they aren't even married yet.
لكنهم غير متزوجين حتى.
Why should she spoil you?
لماذا تعاملكم بهذه الطريقة؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I appreciate the effort.
أعجبني هذا المجهود.
But I will pay for the food.
ولكنني سأدفع ثمن الوجبة.
They were the ones who paid Dad's hospital bill.
أنت من دفع فاتورة المستشفى لوالدي.
This director?
هذا المخرج؟
Hello, I am Baek Su Bin, the eldest son.
مرحبًا، أنا بايك سو بين، الابن الأكبر.
What brings you here, Mr. Director?
ولكن ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا يا مدير؟
I'll meet someone here too.
سأقابل شخصًا هنا أيضًا.
I met you here by chance.
لقد صادفت وجودك هنا.
I understand.
أرى.
Then we will let you go now.
سوف نتركك تذهب إذن.
But they just cancelled on me.
لكنهم ألغوا الحجز معي الآن.
Do you mind if I join you?
هل تمانع إذا انضممت إليك؟
Well, we're having a family dinner.
حسنًا، نحن نتناول وجبة عائلية.
Yongsun is a family.
يونغسونغ هي عائلة واحدة.
Wouldn't that be okay?
ألا يكون ذلك جيدًا؟
Team leader Baek has recently achieved something great.
لقد حقق قائد الفريق بايك شيئًا عظيمًا مؤخرًا.
I was planning to invite her to dinner anyway.
لقد كنت أقصد أن أدعوها لتناول وجبة طعام.
Was that our Su Jeong?
هل فعل سو جونغ ذلك؟
Su Bing's girlfriend is coming.
صديقة سو بين قادمة.
Oh my goodness. It's alright. It's fine.
يا إلهي، لا بأس، لا بأس.
She is a social butterfly.
إنها فراشة اجتماعية.
She is not shy.
إنها ليست خجولة.
Why don't we sit down?
لماذا ليس لدينا مقعد؟
I will tell you what she did, where and when,
سأخبرك ماذا فعلت وأين ومتى
down to the smallest detail.
بالتفصيل الدقيق.
Sounds good. Please sit down. Yes.
يبدو جيدًا. اجلس. نعم.
Thanks to team leader Baek,
شكرًا لقائد الفريق بايك
We were able to convince CEO An.
لقد تمكنا من إقناع الرئيس التنفيذي آن.
Because she is so persistent.
إنها عنيدة للغاية.
I don't know where she got that from.
لا أعلم من أين حصلت على هذا.
She must have gotten it from her wonderful father.
لا بد أنها حصلت على ذلك من والدها المذهل.
They really have a good eye for people.
لديك حقا عين جيدة للناس.
I have a tendency towards that.
أنا أميل إلى أن أكون بهذه الطريقة.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
What do we do now?
ماذا نفعل؟
Ye Na unfortunately cannot come due to an emergency call.
يي نا لا تستطيع الحضور بسبب إرسالية طارئة.
Really? Then we can't change it.
حقا؟ لا يمكننا المساعدة إذن.
His girlfriend is a police officer.
صديقته ضابطة شرطة.
She feels terrible.
إنها تشعر بالرعب.
She congratulates you again on having your plaster cast removed.
تهنئك مرة أخرى على إزالة الجبيرة.
She wants to invite us next time.
إنها تريد أن تعالجينا في المرة القادمة.
Tell her that I appreciate the gesture alone.
أخبرها أنني أقدر هذه البادرة وحدها.
Then I can invite you to this meal today.
ثم، أستطيع أن أدعوك إلى هذه الوجبة اليوم.
Help yourself to plenty.
تناول الكثير من الطعام.
Who said that you─
من قال أنك تستطيع؟
Excuse me!
اعذرني!
Please bring us the menu.
من فضلك أحضر لنا القائمة.
Thank you so much for the food.
شكرا على الوجبة.
Excuse me, Mr. Ban.
عذرا سيد بان.
I wasn't sure, but
لم أكن متأكدا، ولكن
You're interested in my sister? Is that correct?
أنت مهتم بأختي، أليس كذلك؟
My dad told me,
لقد اخبرني والدي
that you are Yongsun's company heir.
أنك خليفة يونغسونغ.
You are an impressive person. Why my sister?
أنت شخص مثير للإعجاب، لماذا أختي؟
I don't know what you think about her,
لا أعرف كيف تفكر بها،
But she is very valuable to us.
لكنها ثمينة جدًا بالنسبة لنا.
She has been through a lot and sacrificed a lot.
لقد مرت بالكثير وضحت بالكثير.
When people looked down on me,
عندما كنت أتعرض للاحتقار،
She played a video game for me instead.
كانت تلعب لعبة فيديو في مكاني.
So if you do this carelessly, just to mess around,
لذا، إذا كنت تفعل هذا بشكل خفيف للعب،
I will not let you get away with this.
لن أسمح لك بالهرب من ذلك.
You don't need to worry about that.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن ذلك.
I don't do this lightly.
أنا لا أفعل هذا باستخفاف.
Madam Chairwoman, what you asked me to do has been done.
السيدة الرئيسة، لقد انتهيت من ما طلبت مني القيام به.
- Already? - Yes.
- بالفعل؟ - نعم.
They are really fast and thorough.
من المؤكد أنك سريع وشامل.
For this reason
هذا هو السبب
I also asked you to clean Director Ban's apartment.
لقد طلبت منك أيضًا تنظيف منزل المدير بان.
They do a good job there too, don't they?
أنت تقوم بعمل جيد هناك أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
Everything is fine, but he said I shouldn't enter his study.
كل شيء جيد، لكنه قال لا تدخل الدراسة.
He said it doesn't need to be cleaned.
قال أنه لا يحتاج إلى تنظيفه.
The study?
الدراسة؟
What does he keep in it?
ماذا يخبئ هناك؟
I'm not sure,
انا لست متأكدا
But it looked like there was video surveillance there.
لكن يبدو أن هناك كاميرا مراقبة أيضًا.
Okay. You can leave now.
حسنًا، يمكنك الذهاب الآن.
[Chief Kwon In Gyeong]
[الرئيس كوان إن كيونغ]
You wanted to see me, Madam Chairwoman.
لقد أردت رؤيتي، سيدتي الرئيسة.
You can go in now.
يمكنك المضي قدما في الداخل.
Once we're finished here,
بمجرد الانتهاء من هنا،
We're going to Director Ban's apartment.
دعونا نذهب إلى منزل المدير بان.
What's this all about so suddenly?
ما الأمر فجأة؟
I need to check his study.
أريد التحقق من دراسته.
He doesn't let anyone in there.
لا يسمح لأحد بالدخول إلى هناك.
I'm curious what important stuff he has there.
أنا فضولي لمعرفة الأشياء المهمة التي لديه هناك.
I will inform Director Ban.
سأخبر المخرج بان.
No.
لا.
That's not necessary.
هذا ليس ضروريا.
Where are your father and your brother?
أين والدك وأخوك؟
I let her go because I have something to say.
تركتهم يذهبون لأنني أردت أن أقول شيئًا.
What exactly do you think?
ماذا تفكر بالضبط؟
Why did you come here?
لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟
I thought we had finished the subject last time.
اعتقدت أننا انتهينا من الحديث في المرة السابقة.
I thought you understood.
اعتقدت أنك فهمت.
It was because I was afraid.
لأنني كنت خائفة.
While I behave so foolishly,
بينما كنت أتصرف بغباء،
and you would like another one
إذا أتيت لتحب شخصًا آخر،
What should I do then?
ماذا سأفعل؟
I don't like that.
انا لا احب ذلك.
Understanding does not mean that...
الفهم لا يعني
I have no feelings anymore.
لم يعد لدي مشاعر.
Yes, Chief.
نعم يا رئيس.
Once the event ends,
بمجرد انتهاء الحدث،
The chairwoman wants to visit your apartment.
ستقوم رئيسة اللجنة بزيارة منزلك
She's coming to my house?
إنها قادمة إلى منزلي؟
Yes. We'll leave in two hours.
نعم، سنغادر بعد ساعتين.
She seems to think
يبدو أنها تفكر
that there is something in your study.
هناك شيء في دراستك
I have to go home immediately.
أريد أن أعود إلى المنزل فوراً.
What's up?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
What's wrong with her coming to your house?
ما المشكلة في مجيئها إلى مكانك؟
The study.
الدراسة.
She will find out that it...
اكتشفت أن هناك...
Calm down for a moment.
اهدأ للحظة.
Ahjummoni, please. Ahjummoni...
جدتي، من فضلك. جدتي...
Forgive me just once, Ahjummoni.
سامحيني مرة واحدة فقط يا جدتي
Don't do that, Ahjummoni.
لا تفعلي ذلك يا جدتي
Oh my! Oh my!
الجدة! الجدة!
Everything could burn and disappear.
كل شيء يمكن أن يحترق ويختفي.
The things I value.
الأشياء التي أقدرها.
- Step aside. - And what if you proceed that way?
- تحرك. - وإذا ذهبت هكذا؟
Do you have a plan?
هل لديك خطة؟
Let's buy some time first.
دعونا نشتري الوقت الآن.
[2024 Future Energy Industry Expo]
[معرض صناعة الطاقة المستقبلية 2024]
Madam Chairwoman.
رئيسة.
Good day.
مرحبًا.
You remember me, don't you? I'm Shin Won.
هل تتذكرني، أليس كذلك؟ أنا سين وون.
Kim Shin Won.
كيم سين وون.
Yes.
نعم.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
I've heard that you're still friends with Director Ban.
سمعت أنك لا تزال قريبًا من المخرج بان.
Yes, of course.
نعم بالطبع.
We are basically like brothers.
نحن في الأساس مثل الإخوة.
Since he started working at the department store,
نظرًا لأنه يعمل في المتجر،
We can spend more time together.
نحن قادرون على قضاء الوقت معًا أكثر.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Incidentally, you haven't changed at all.
بالمناسبة، أنت لم تتغير على الإطلاق.
Does time pass you by without leaving a trace?
هل مرور الزمن لا ينطبق عليك؟
The PR team at headquarters should try harder.
يحتاج فريق العلاقات العامة في المقر الرئيسي إلى العمل بشكل أكثر جدية.
Your photos don't do it justice.
صورك لا تظهر العدالة.
They look so young and beautiful.
أنت تبدو شابًا وجميلًا جدًا.
They're still good at chatting.
أنت لا تزال جيدًا في التغازل.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
By the way, what brings you here?
بالمناسبة، ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Oh, yes, I was just in the area.
أوه، حسنًا، لقد كنت في المنطقة للتو.
Have you eaten yet, Madam Chairwoman?
هل أكلت يا رئيسة؟
If not, would you like to join me?
إذا لم تقم بذلك، هل ترغب في الانضمام إلي؟
When would I ever again
متى سأصل إلى ذلك؟
have the honor of going out to dinner with you?
هل لي أن أتشرف بتناول وجبة طعام معك مرة أخرى؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
But I have to go. I'm busy.
لكن عليّ أن أبدأ، فأنا مشغول.
Madam Chairwoman.
رئيسة.
How about a cup of tea?
ماذا عن شرب الشاي للحظة إذن؟
Stop taking up any more of my time.
توقف عن أخذ المزيد من وقتي.
P-Take care of yourself.
ت- اعتني بنفسك.
[Bbanjju]
[بانجو]
Yes, I tried to stop her,
نعم، لقد حاولت إيقافها
But going out to eat with her is going too far.
لكن أعتقد أن تناول الطعام معها أمر مبالغ فيه.
What exactly is going on?
ماذا يحدث بالضبط؟
If you park your truck here,
إذا تركت شاحنتك هنا،
What about the other cars?
ماذا عن السيارات الأخرى؟
Toilet?
مرحاض؟
I will call the police if you do not come immediately.
سأتصل بالشرطة إذا لم تأت الآن.
A lot of time has passed.
لقد مر الكثير من الوقت.
Should I postpone the visit to the director's house?
هل يجب علي تأجيل الزيارة إلى منزل المدير؟
That's fine.
لا بأس.
It would only take a moment anyway.
سيستغرق الأمر لحظة على أية حال.
They have another appointment after that.
لديك موعد آخر بعد ذلك أيضًا.
Why are we still talking?
لماذا لا نزال نتحدث؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm sorry, I was in such a hurry.
أنا آسف، لقد كنت في عجلة من أمري.
I think a car could easily fit through here.
أعتقد أن السيارة يمكن أن تمر بسهولة من هنا.
How strange.
كم هو غريب.
What does "parked in the middle of the street" mean?
ماذا تقصد بالوقوف في منتصف الطريق؟
Did I do that?
هل فعلت؟
But I guess you can't...
لكن أعتقد أنك لا تستطيع...
You can't just drive off like that.
لا يمكنك الذهاب هكذا فقط.
Anyway. Drive your truck away now.
مهما يكن، انقل شاحنتك الآن.
Okay, okay.
حسنًا، حسنًا.
I feel really bad, by the way.
أنا أشعر بالرعب حقًا، بالمناسبة.
Shall I cut you some sashimi?
هل يجب أن أقطع لك بعض الساشيمي؟
I have a load of fish, directly from Jeju─
لدي طن من الأسماك مباشرة من جيجو-
Get your truck out of the way and stop this nonsense!
انظر! توقف عن الكلام الفارغ وحرك الشاحنة!
I guess you don't want to.
أعتقد أنك لا تريد ذلك.
All right! Okay.
لقد حصلت عليه!حسنا.
I, Su Jeong.
نعم ، سو جونغ.
I did my best, but...
لقد بذلت قصارى جهدي، ولكن...
So why are you trying to stop the chairwoman?
إذن، لماذا تحاولون إيقاف رئيسة اللجنة؟
Will you tell me later?
ستخبرني لاحقا؟
Huh? Okay.
هاه؟ حسنا.
Hello Hello...
مرحبا؟ مرحبا...
Was?
ماذا؟
I can't believe I ran into you here by chance.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنني التقيت بك هنا.
I know. What brings you here?
انا أعلم، ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Su Jeong asked me for a favor.
لقد طلب مني سو جونغ خدمة.
Oh? Ju Yeon also asked me for a favor.
هاه؟ جو يون طلبت مني خدمة.
Really?
حقًا؟
I thought they weren't close anymore.
اعتقدت أنهم لم يعودوا قريبين بعد الآن.
Was I wrong?
هل كنت مخطئا؟
It's definitely good to see you.
على أية حال، يسعدني رؤيتك.
I'm leaving now.
سأذهب الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
- Drive carefully. - Okay.
- قيادة آمنة. - حسنا.
If she was so happy to see me,
لو كانت سعيدة جدًا لرؤيتي،
She could have gotten out briefly.
كان ينبغي لها أن تخرج لفترة وجيزة.
What are you doing? Pack the rest of your things.
ماذا تفعل؟ قم بتحميل بقية الأشياء.
Yes, I should do that.
نعم يجب علي ذلك.
We are in the parking garage.
نحن في موقف السيارات.
You are now in front of the building.
إنهم أمام المبنى الآن.
Already?
بالفعل؟
We've taken the important things away, right?
لقد نقلنا الأشياء المهمة، أليس كذلك؟
What should we do with the rest?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل بالباقي؟
If we block the door to this room─
إذا قمنا بسد باب هذه الغرفة-
She is already suspicious.
إنها بالفعل مشبوهة.
She won't simply go back.
إنها لن تعود أبدًا.
What should we do?
ماذا ينبغي لنا أن نفعل إذن؟
I came to see how you live.
لقد جئت لأرى كيف تعيش.
I suspect you're about to leave.
أعتقد أنك كنت على وشك المغادرة.
Yes.
نعم.
I would like to invite you next time, if that would be alright.
أود أن أدعوك في المرة القادمة إذا كان ذلك مناسبًا-
You do not need to be invited to inspect your apartment.
لا حاجة إلى أن تتم دعوتك لزيارة مكانك.
Why?
لماذا؟
Is there a reason why I shouldn't go to your apartment?
هل هناك سبب يمنعني من دخول مكانك؟
No.
لا.
Then let's go up together if it's nothing important.
دعونا نصعد معًا إذا لم يكن هناك شيء عاجل.
Take me to the study.
خذني إلى الدراسة.
Okay.
تمام.
It looks normal.
يبدو طبيعيا.
I'm curious why you don't let her clean this room.
أنا فضولي لماذا لا تسمح لها بتنظيف هذه الغرفة.
Are you hiding...
هل أنت...
Something in here?
هل تخفي شيئا هنا؟
Huh!
هاه؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'd rather go.
سأغادر أولا.
You don't want to go and meet her now.
لا تريد أن تغادر الآن وتلتقي بها.
Stay here.
ابقى هنا.
I thought you were going to do something stupid again.
اعتقدت أنك تفعل شيئًا سخيفًا مرة أخرى.
Did you try to hide this?
هل كنت تحاول إخفاء هذا؟
I know you wouldn't be happy...
أعلم أنك لن تكون سعيدًا
If you knew I had the photo.
لو كنت تعلم أن لدي تلك الصورة.
I don't have the right...
ليس لدي الحق في
to cry or to be sad.
أبكي أو أشعر بالحزن.
Yes.
نعم.
So why did you keep it if you knew that?
فلماذا احتفظت به إذا كنت تعرف ذلك؟
I know...
أنا أعرف...
I do not have the right to
ليس لدي الحق
But I wanted to keep at least one photo.
ولكنني أردت الاحتفاظ بصورة، على الأقل.
Because I miss her so much.
لأنني أفتقدهم كثيرًا.
Do you think you have the right to miss her?
هل تعتقد أن لديك الحق في تفويتهم؟
If you hadn't been there,
لو لم يكن لك،
My son would still be here.
ابني سوف يظل هنا.
Not this stupid photo,
ليس هذه الصورة الغبية،
but my real son!
لكن ابني الحقيقي!
Weak, complete idiot.
اللقيط الضعيف.
From now on, keep a closer eye on him.
ابقي عينك عليه عن كثب من الآن فصاعدا.
Should I have someone monitor him?
هل يجب أن أطلب من شخص أن يراقبه؟
I have you, who are watching him.
أريدك أن تشاهده.
Who else do we need?
من نحتاج اليه ايضا؟
Yes, I will monitor him more closely.
نعم سأراقبه عن كثب.
Be careful. You will get hurt.
كن حذرا، سوف تؤذي نفسك.
You know that my parents died in a car accident, right?
هل تعلم أن والدي ماتوا في حادث سيارة، أليس كذلك؟
We were on our way to an anime event.
كنا في طريقنا لحضور حدث أنمي.
They were both busy,
لقد كانا مشغولين كلاهما
But I begged her to let me leave.
لكنني توسلت إليهم لأنني أردت أن أذهب.
That's when we got into an accident on the way.
لقد تعرضنا لحادث على الطريق.
Thanks to their protection, I survived.
بفضل حمايتهم، نجوت.
But they died in the accident.
لكنهم ماتوا في حادث
in which they shouldn't have been because of me.
لم يكن ينبغي لهم أن يكونوا هنا بسببي.
My grandmother actually lost her only son because of me.
لقد فقدت جدتي ابنها الوحيد بسببي.
So I decided to make it up to them.
لذلك قررت أن أعوضها.
To become the person she wants to be, the one who replaces my father.
لتصبح الشخص الذي تريده وتحل محل الأب.
Director.
مخرج.
But even after that
ولكن حتى بعد ذلك،
I still couldn't give up my joy.
لا أستطيع أن أتخلى عن فرحتي حتى الآن.
The next volume of my favorite cartoon
المجلد القادم من الرسوم المتحركة المفضلة لدي،
and the new song and the bands' show.
والأغنية الجديدة والعرض الجديد للفرقة.
I need things like that...
كنت بحاجة لأشياء مثل هذه
to look forward to tomorrow.
لنتطلع إلى الغد.
Although nobody loved me, I was content.
على الرغم من أن لا أحد يحبني، إلا أنني شعرت بالرضا.
And that's why
لهذا السبب...
I was truly happy when you showed me at the fountain
عندما قلت لي أن أحب الأشياء التي أحبها
You said that I should like things,
كل ما أريده أمام النافورة،
that I like.
لقد كنت سعيدا حقا.
That's what I meant too.
لقد قصدت ذلك.
You have
لقد نظرت...
She really looked happy back then.
سعيدة حقا إذن.
I wanted you to continue being happy.
أردت أن تستمر في سعادتك.
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
I hid the things I like for a long time.
لقد قمت بإخفاء أشياء أحببتها لفترة طويلة.
Because everything I liked was a secret.
لأن كل ما أعجبني كان سرا.
That's why I couldn't tell you, but
ولهذا السبب لم أتمكن من إخبارك، ولكن...
I really like you a lot, Baek Su Jeong.
ولكنني أحبك كثيرًا، بايك سو جونغ.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep this to myself.
أنا آسف لأنني لم أتمكن من السيطرة عليه.
Thank you for what you did today.
شكرا لك على اليوم.
There's my daughter.
هناك ابنتي.
Yes, Dad. You're home.
نعم يا أبي، لقد كنت في المنزل.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
You had asked me to receive packages.
لقد طلبت مني أن أتلقى الطرود.
The people were there, delivered them, and left again.
جاء الناس لتسليمهم ثم رحلوا.
Ah, yes. That's right.
أوه نعم، هذا صحيح.
Are you sick?
هل انت مريض؟
You had a date. You look terrible.
لقد كنت تقابل شخصًا ما، وتبدو فظيعًا.
No, I am not ill.
لا، أنا لست مريضًا.
I asked her to take the packages up to the attic.
طلبت منهم أن يضعوا الطرود في العلية.
Why was there so much stuff?
لماذا كان هناك الكثير من الأشياء؟
Someone I know asked me to store them temporarily.
طلب مني أحد معارفي أن أحتفظ بها لفترة وجيزة.
He will bring her back soon.
سوف يعيدونهم قريبا.
We don't use the room anyway.
نحن لا نستخدم تلك المساحة، على أية حال.
I don't care if they stay longer, but
لا أمانع في إبقاءهم هناك لفترة طويلة، لكن
You're sure you're okay, right?
أنت متأكد أنك بخير، أليس كذلك؟
Of course. Why shouldn't I be doing well?
بالطبع، لماذا لا أكون بخير؟
Su Jeong.
سو جونغ.
Hm?
نعم؟
Do you know,
أنت تعرف...
When you smile like that, it breaks my heart.
رؤية ابتسامتك بهذه الطريقة تكسر قلبي.
Because I'm not good enough
لأنني لست جيدا بما فيه الكفاية،
And because you can't rely on me...
ولأنك لا تستطيع الاعتماد علي...
Because you can't tell me if anything is wrong,
نظرًا لأنه لا يمكنك أن تخبرني عندما يحدث شيء ما،
I wonder if that's why you're smiling like that.
أتساءل هل كل ما تفعله هو الابتسامة هكذا.
Also...
لذا...
Dad,
أب،
Please don't worry, it's nothing.
من فضلك لا تقلق، لا شيء يحدث.
I'm just tired because I've been traveling for a while.
أنا متعب فقط لأنني كنت خارجًا لفترة من الوقت.
Okay, then. Go to your room and rest.
حسنًا إذًا، اذهب إلى الداخل واسترح.
Then you go to your room too.
أنت تذهب أيضاً
Okay.
تمام.
You smile a lot.
لقد كنت تبتسم كثيرًا
You don't usually smile.
أنت لا تبتسم عادة.
What can I do to make you feel better?
كيف يمكنني أن أجعلك تشعر بتحسن؟
Isn't it tiring to work alone?
أليس العمل بمفردك صعبًا؟
And it's lonely, too.
إنه وحيد أيضًا
I hid the things I like for a long time.
لقد قمت بإخفاء أشياء أحببتها لفترة طويلة.
Because everything I liked was a secret.
لأن كل ما أعجبني كان سرًا
That's why I couldn't tell you, but
لهذا السبب لا أستطيع أن أخبرك، ولكن...
I really like you a lot, Baek Su Jeong.
لكنني أحبك كثيرًا، بايك سو جونغ.
♫
♫ الحب مثل المعجزة ♫
I know that's crazy, but
أعلم أن هذا جنون أيضًا، ولكن
I can remember everything.
أتذكر كل شيء
That was
ذلك كان...
My first kiss.
قبلتي الأولى
♫
♫ اللحظات الجميلة التي مرت ♫
The phone is switched off.
تم إيقاف تشغيل الهاتف.
You will be redirected to your voicemail...
سيتم توصيلك بالبريد الصوتي...
♫
♫ سأقولها الليلة ♫
I like you.
أنا معجب بك
Director.
مخرج.
Director, are you in there?
السيد المخرج هل أنت هناك؟
I would like to ask you something.
أريد أن أسألك شيئا.
♫
♫ في نهاية اللحظات الخافتة ♫
So this is where you are.
ها أنت ذا.
Baek Su Jeong.
السيدة بايك.
I wanted to know something.
لقد كنت فضوليًا بشأن شيء ما.
That's why I'm here.
لهذا السبب جئت.
When you remembered that you kissed me,
عندما تذكرت أنك قبلتني،
Why did you flee here then?
لماذا ركضت كل هذه المسافة إلى هنا؟
You knew it was crazy to do that.
لقد عرفت أن هذا كان شيئًا مجنونًا للقيام به.
So, if you showed up dressed like that, the things you were hiding,
إذا أتيت بهذا الشكل، فإن الأشياء التي أخفيتها...
the secrets you have so carefully kept,
الأسرار التي عملت بجد للحفاظ عليها
They can be uncovered. You knew that.
كان من الممكن أن يتم الكشف عن ذلك. لقد كنت تعرف ذلك.
So why did you come?
إذن لماذا أتيت؟
Just because you like me?
فقط لأنك تحبني؟
For that reason alone?
لهذا السبب واحد؟
Would that be okay?
هل ستكون بخير؟
Our relationship could be exposed at any time
علاقتنا قد تنكشف في أي وقت
And that could be a problem for your dream of becoming Yongsung's successor.
وقد يكون ذلك مشكلة بالنسبة لحلمك
represent.
يصبح خليفة يونغسونغ.
I
أنا...
I think that would be okay.
أعتقد أنني سأكون بخير
as long as I have you.
ما دامت عندي أنت.
As long as you like me.
طالما أنك تحبني.
All right then.
حسنًا.
If that is the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
I will become your biggest secret.
سأصبح سرك الأكبر.
You said everything you like is a secret.
قلت أن كل ما تحبه هو سر.
That means I like you too.
وهذا يعني أنني أحبك أيضًا.
[Black Dragon]
[التنين الأسود]
My Dearest Nemesis
[عدوتي العزيزة]
♫ Yeah, yeah ♫
♫ نعم، نعم ♫
[We thank Hong Jong Hyeon for his guest appearance]
[نشكر هونغ جونغ هيون على الظهور الخاص]
♫ Honestly, I don't know, oh, no ♫
♫ بصراحة، لا أعرف، أوه، لا ♫
♫ I think I'm losing my mind ♫
♫ أعتقد أنني أفقد عقلي ♫
♫ Oh, damn ♫
♫ يا إلهي ♫
♫ Exactly like that ♫
♫ أعجبني هذا ♫
♫ What am I going to do? I don't know ♫
♫ ماذا أفعل؟ لا أعرف ♫
♫ I'm falling more and more in love with you, oh, tonight ♫
♫ استمر في الوقوع في الحب، أوه، الليلة ♫
♫ Shine a light on my heart ♫
♫ أشرق نورًا على قلبي ♫
You do realize that we need to be more careful at work, right?
أنت تعلم أنه يتعين علينا أن نكون أكثر حذرا في العمل، أليس كذلك؟
We'll never get caught, don't worry.
لن يتم القبض علينا أبدًا. لا تقلق.
They say office romances are hell.
يقولون أن الرومانسية في المكتب أشبه بالجحيم.
Working life is hell.
الجحيم في العمل
You should sign this now.
وافق عليه الآن
You're too good at improvising.
أنت جيد جدًا في الارتجال.
What can I do to make you feel better?
كيف يمكنني أن أجعلك تشعر بتحسن؟
Do you really have a girlfriend?
هل أنت تواعد حقا؟
Don't try to find out too much. It would only hurt you.
لا تحاول أن تعرف الكثير، فسوف تتأذى.
Ju Yeon finally looks truly happy.
جو يون تبدو سعيدة حقًا أخيرًا.
What if they find out who the other one is?
ماذا لو اكتشفوا من هو الشخص الآخر؟
♫
♫ لم أنساك ولو للحظة ♫
♫ Only you ♫
♫ أنت فقط ♫
♫ I keep falling in love ♫
♫ استمر في الوقوع في الحب ♫